Guide to the Sara and Gerald Murphy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Objects, 1915-1967; Series V; 20.59 linear feet (26 boxes)
  - Bags
    - Black leather handbag with gold metal clasp and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag, 1940s (Box 74)
      Leather, fabric, and metal; 8 x 10 inches
      Made by Mark Cross; tan leather interior includes pocket mirror
    - Fur handbag with brown leather trim and handles with drawstring closing and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag, circa 1939 (Box 72)
      Fur, leather, and metal; 7.5 x 12 x 6.25 inches
      Made by Mark Cross (patent number 118076)
    - Leather handbag with woven textile body and brown leather trim and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag, undated (Box 75)
      Leather, wool, and metal; 11.5 x 10.5 x 4 inches
    - Red alligator leather handbag with spaghetti straps and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag, after 1950 (Box 74)
      Leather and metal; embossed "Honoria Donnelly"
    - Peach silk envelope bag embroidered with birds and "HD - Happy Birthday - 29", 1946 (Box 70)
      Silk and cotton; 5 x 10.5 inches
    - Leather beaded pouch with metal bells, undated (Box 69)
      Leather, plastic, metal; 4.5 x 4 inches
    - White canvas bag with rope handles, drawstring closing, and embroidered anchor, undated (Box 76)
      Canvas, rope, and metal; 13 x 8 inches
    - Black canvas bag with rope handles, undated (Box 76)
      Canvas, rope, and metal; 12.25 x 10.5 inches
    - Black and white striped canvas bag with rope drawstring, undated (Box 76)
      Canvas, rope, metal; 13 x 13 inches
    - White duffle bag with "Air Mail, Macy Line" stenciled on it, undated (Box 76)
      Cotton and metal; 10.5 x 7 inches
    - Paisley toiletry bag, undated (Box 76)
      Fabric, metal, and plastic; 6 x 10 inches
    - Brown alligator leather collar box, undated (Box 77)
      Leather; 6.5 x 6.5 inches
      Made by Mark Cross London; tan leather interior
    - Leather cordovan jewelry case stamped "A.S.W." (Adeline Sherman Wiborg) and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag, before 1917 (Box 77)
      Leather, satin, and metal; 8 x 4 inches
    - Green leather traveler's map case stamped "Honoria Murphy, care Guaranty Trust Company", undated
      Leather, plastic, and paper; 10.5 x 10 inches
      Made by Mark Cross; contains map of France; tabbed file pockets and pencil loops
    - Garment bags, undated
      Satin and lace; 12 x 8 and 20 x 14
    - Black leather luggage tag, undated (Box 84, Folder 931)
      Leather, plastic, and paper; 1.5 x 2 inches
      Insert reads "Gerald Murphy, President, Mark Cross Company"
  - Watches, Jewelry, Eyewear, and Cigarette Cases
    - Mark Cross pocket watch with Roman numerals, undated (Box 78)
      Metal and glass; 2.75 x 4 inches
    - Mark Cross pocket watch with Arabic numerals, undated (Box 78)
      Metal and glass; 3 x 4 inches
      Owned by Honoria Murphy Donnelly
    - Cartier wrist watch in Movado case, 1925 (Box 78)
      Metal, leather, glass; 5.5 x 2.5 inches
      Inscribed "B.M.W. from O.W.F. 1925"
    - Traveling clock in blue leather case, undated (Box 79)
      Leather, metal, and glass; 3.5 x 4 inches
      Made in France
    - Traveling clock in green leather case, undated (Box 78)
      Leather, metal, and glass; 4 x 4 inches
      Made by L. Leroy & Co. Paris; No. 14073
    - Traveling clock in brown alligator leather case, undated (Box 78)
      Leather, cloth, metal, and glass; 4.5 x 4.5
    - Traveling clock in brown leather case with "H.M." monogram, undated (Box 78)
      Leather, glass, and metal; 4.5 x 3.0 inches
      Made by Le Coultre
    - Tortoiseshell cigarette case with metal inlay decoration and "S" on front, undated (Box 78)
      Plastic and metal; 4 x 2 inches
    - Monogrammed cigarette cases, undated (Box 77)
      Wood and metal; 3 x 7.25 inches
      Metal initials affixed to wooden boxes
    - Wooden cigarette case, undated (Box 77)
      Wood; 2.75 x 3.25 inches
    - Pearl necklace, undated (Box 80)
    - Choker necklace made with fake pearls and emeralds, undated (Box 80)
      Plastic, metal, and fabric cord; missing several beads
    - White beaded necklace, undated (Box 80)
      Glass or stone
    - Pink beaded necklace, undated (Box 78)
    - Turquoise beaded choker necklace, undated (Box 78)
      Plastic beads and metal
    - Gold choker necklace, undated (Box 78)
      Metal beads painted gold
    - Gold bead necklace, undated (Box 78)
      Glass painted with gold design and metal
    - Pink plastic beaded necklace, undated (Box 78)
      Plastic
    - Nautical themed charm bracelet, undated (Box 78)
      Metal
    - Bracelet and various charms, undated (Box 78)
      Metal, shell, and glass
    - Bracelet with polished stones, undated (Box 78)
      Metal and stones; missing one stone
    - Gold anklet, undated (Box 78)
      Gold; made by Forstner
    - Gold and pearl hairpin, undated (Box 78)
      Gold and pearls; 2.0 inches
    - Pearl brooch, undated (Box 78)
      Pearls and metal
    - Daisy brooch, undated (Box 78)
      Metal, glass; 2.75 x 2.75 inches
    - Celtic knot brooch, undated (Box 78)
    - Ear clips, undated (Box 78)
      Metal and glass
    - Various clips, undated (Box 78)
    - Clips in shape of "G" and "S", undated (Box 78)
    - Lighter on chain, undated (Box 78)
      Metal; 1.0 x 0.5 inches
    - Buttons with monogram "S.A.W." (Sara Adeline Wiborg), undated (Box 78)
      Metal; made by "Waldron & Carroll N.Y."
    - Decorative buttons, undated (Box 78)
    - Decorative buckles, undated (Box 78)
    - Cuff links engraved with "B" and "H", undated (Box 78)
    - Collar buttons in small leather case with "B.M." (Baoth Murphy) written on bottom, undated (Box 78)
      Ivory and metal; 3.25 x 2 inches
      Two complete sets (one ivory and one metal "Krementz") and one incomplete set (Brooks Brothers)
    - Collar pin with "G.M." (Gerald Murphy) monogram tag, undated (Box 78)
      Metal; 2 inches
    - Black leather pouch with white stitching and key ring with various keys, undated (Box 80)
      Leather, metal, and paper; 4.75 x 3 inches
      Made by Mark Cross; monogrammed with "S.W.M." (Sara Wiborg Murphy) and includes keys for "Patrick's small valise" and "Victrola," Louis Vuitton keys, and other keys
    - Painted wooden key ring with image of desk on one side and "La Clé de mon Bureau" on the other side, undated (Box 78)
      Wood, metal, and paper; 1 x 2.5 inches
    - Orange ornament embossed with image of woman smelling flower, undated (Box 78)
      Plastic; 1.25 x 1.75 inches
    - Shell pendant, undated (Box 78)
    - Extra feathers for Gerald Murphy's hats, undated (Box 84, Folder 932)
    - Pieces of broken jewellery, undated (Box 84, Folder 933)
    - Three birds figurines, undated (Box 78)
      Glass and wire
    - Beads, undated (Box 78)
      Glass and stone
    - Folding spectacles in leather case, undated (Box 78)
      Glass, leather, plastic, and metal; 3.25 x 2.25 inches
      Bought at E.B. Meyrowitz, Paris
    - Pince-nez, undated (Box 78)
      Plastic and metal; 4.5 x 1.75 inches
    - Opera glasses with lens cleaner, undated (Box 80)
      Metal, leather, and glass; 3.25 x 1.25 inches
      Made by "R.T."
    - Opera glasses in leather case, circa 1945 (Box 80)
      Metal, plastic, and glass; 2.5 x 4 inches
      Opera glasses "Jupiter Junior" model "Made in Occupied Japan" by American Optical Company; leather case made by Mark Cross
    - Opera glasses in leather case, undated (Box 80)
      Leather, metal, plastic; 4 x 1.5 inches
      Made by Mirakel
  - Household Objects
    - Silver tray with "Wiborg" engraved on face, undated
      Silver; 12 x 9 inches
    - Forbes Silver Plate Company sugar bowl, undated (Box 79)
      Silver; 3.5 x 4 inches
      Model 658; handle broken
    - Reed & Barton small lamp and stand, undated (Box 79)
      Silver; 2.5 x 3 and 3.5 x 3.5 inches
      Model 1412 and N101 1265
    - Jiggers in leather case, undated (Box 80)
      Metal and leather; 2.5 x 2 inches
      Made by Mark Cross England; leather case contains four jiggers
    - Silver juicer, undated (Box 80)
      Silver; 4.5 x 3.75
    - Silver and glass juicer, undated (Box 79)
      Silver and glass; 4 x 3 inches
    - "Ritter Citro" fruit wedge press, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 2.5 x 2.5 inches
      Made in Germany
    - Silver double-sided measuring cup, undated (Box 80)
      Silver; 3.75 x 2 inches
      Made by "S. Kirk & Son"
    - Swizzle sticks, long-handled spoons, and ice masher, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 10.5 inches
    - Bottle opener, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 4 x 1.5 inches
    - Green handled bottle opener, undated (Box 80)
      Wood and metal; 3.75 x 1.25 inches
    - Green handled corkscrew, undated (Box 80)
      Wood and metal; 3.5 x 4.25 inches
    - Jackknife bottle opener and corkscrew, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 7 x 1 inches
    - Zig Zag corkscrew, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 6.5 x 3 inches
      "BTE S.G.D.G., M & M. Dep."
    - Corkscrew and bottle opener, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 5 x 1.5 inches
      Made by Irvinware in Italy
    - Cork with metal handle, undated (Box 80)
      Cork and metal; 3 x 2 inches
    - Mechanical claw for handling garnishes, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 5 x 1.25 inches
    - Metal clamp or press, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 4 x 5 inches
    - Metal bracket and screws, undated (Box 81)
    - Jackknife shaped like bottle, undated (Box 80)
      Metal and shell; 3.5 x 1.0 inches
      Metal inlay decor of anchor
    - Oyster knife in leather case, undated (Box 81)
      Wood, metal, and leather; 5.5 x 1.25 inches
      Engraved "CALINO Huitres Depose"
    - Rostfrei filet knife with bone handle and leather sheath, undated (Box 81)
      Bone, stainless steel, and leather; 6.25 x 0.5 inches
    - Metal napkin rings, undated (Box 80)
      Metal; 1.5 x 3 inches
      Made by Brevete; wire formed into initials "G", "S," and "P"
    - Plastic napkin rings, undated (Box 80)
      Plastic; 2 x 2 inches
      Made by WAMA company; imprinted with initials "S" and "H"
    - Hand-carved rabbit napkin ring, undated (Box 80)
      Wood; 4 x 2.5 inches
    - Diamond and heart-shaped plates, undated (Box 84, Folder 934)
      Mahogany; 5.75 x 5.75 and 7.5 x 7.5 inches
      Made in Haiti
    - Hand carved wooden spoons, undated (Box 81)
      Wood; 8.5 x 2 inches
    - Wooden bowl, undated (Box 79)
      Wood; 4 x 5 inches
    - Wooden containers, undated (Box 79)
      Wood; 6.5 x 2.5 inches
    - Wooden shaker, undated (Box 79)
      Wood; 4 x 1.5 inches
    - Mirror with black pebbled leather frame and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag, undated (Box 84, Folder 935)
      Leather, glass, and metal; 7.5 x 6 inches
    - Green leather picture frame and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag, undated (Box 84, Folder 936)
      Leather and glass; 7.5 x 9.5 inches
      Made by Mark Cross Italy
    - Brown leather trifold photo display case with stamped gold motif, undated (Box 84, Folder 937)
      Leather, plastic, and fabric; 7 x 9 inches
    - Blue leather picture frame, undated (Box 85, Folder 938)
      Leather and plastic; 7 x 4 inches
    - Metal picture frame, undated (Box 85, Folder 939)
      Metal, velvet, and glass; 10.5 x 8 inches
    - Metal picture frame with cubic zirconia around the outside of the frame, undated (Box 85, Folder 940)
      Metal and glass; 6 x 3.5 inches
    - Framed Persian watercolor, undated (Box 85, Folder 941)
      Paper, metal, and glass; 8 x 11.5 inches
    - Hand carved toothpicks, undated (Box 81)
      Wood; 5 x 1 inches
      Enclosed notecard reads "Gerald Murphy said these were hand carved by American Indians and he served them in martinis with green olive stuffed with almond speared through them"
    - Circular cutting board with handle, undated (Box 85, Folder 942)
      Wood; 8.5 x 5.5
    - Wooden spoons, undated (Box 81)
      Wood; 9.5 x 1.5 inches
    - Carved light switch plate, undated (Box 86, Folder 943)
      Wood; 5 x 7.75 inches
    - Yellow pillow, undated (Box 77)
      Silk and lace; 2.75 x 8 inches
    - White lace linens, undated (Box 82)
      Lace; 22 x 14 inches
    - Yellow tea towels monogrammed "S.M.", undated (Box 82)
      Fabric; 15 x 23 inches
    - Table runner and circular place mats used by Murphys while living in Antibes, circa 1920
      Fabric; 15 x 25 and 9 x 9 inches
      Black with floral embroidery
    - Tablecloths, undated
      Cotton; 50 x 76 inches
      Used on cover of "Villa America Cookbook"
    - Sewing needles and other related items in metal "Ed. Laurens" cigarette box, undated (Box 78)
      Metal, paper, and thread; 3.25 x 2.75 inches
      Label on box reads "Woven Marking Names 'Honoria'"
    - Sewing needles and straight pins in diaper pin tin, undated (Box 78)
      Metal and paper; 2.25 x 2 inches
    - Pin cushion with crown and "Paris" embroidered on it, undated (Box 77)
      Fabric; 5 x 5 inches
  - Children's Toys and Sports Equipment
    - Cartridge belt, undated (Box 81)
      Leather, metal, and glass; 39 x 4 inches
      Includes bullets, pouch, circular metal hooks from which hang compass, pocket knife, sheathed knife
    - Sealskin ski breaks, circa 1925 (Box 81)
      Seal skin, metal, and canvas; 94 x 2.5 inches
      Gift to Murphy children from Ernest Hemingway
    - Tech-Bilt etching set owned by Patrick Murphy, before 1937 (Box 83)
      Cardboard, paper, plastic, metal, wood, felt, and ink; 13 x 9.5 inches
      Includes: etching pens, ink roller, ink applicator, magnifying glass, and plastic plates with Patrick Murphy's etching of Ernest Hemingway
    - Miniatures owned by Patrick Murphy, before 1937 (Box 80)
    - Wooden dog carved by Patrick Murphy, before 1937 (Box 80)
    - Small metal toy airplane, undated (Box 86, Folder 944)
      Metal; 4.0 x 4.0 inches
    - Small statue of horses, undated (Box 80)
      Porcelain; 2.75 x 1.0 inches
    - Plastic tumblers and small wooden barrel, undated (Box 80)
      Plastic and wood; 1.75 x 1.5 inches
  - Other Objects
    - Splatter mask from WWI, 1917 (Box 82)
      Metal, leather, glass and felt; 6 x 7 inches
      Belonged to Frederic Murphy
    - Silver pitcher engraved "From the Boys of the Fifth Provisional Company, December 14th, 1918, Garden City, Long Island, N.Y." (Box 87)
      Silver; 10.0 x 7.5 inches
    - Small plaque with image of Levi Addison Ault, Frank Wiborg, and shield with "Golden Anniversary The Ault & Wiborg Co., Fifty years of Service to Industry" written across the bottom, 1928 (Box 77)
    - Silver commemorative plaque mounted on wood engraved "To, Gerald Murphy, President, In Appreciation for his Constant Inspiration and Understanding, from, The Mark Cross Employees, of the Centenary Year 1945" and felt Mark Cross merchandise bag
      Silver and wood; 16.0 x 13.0 inches
    - Plaque with Mark Cross England trademark logo and Mark Cross merchandise bag, circa 1940
      Wood and plastic; 10 x 12 inches
    - Three-dimensional Mark Cross England trademark logo in lucite, circa 1940 (Box 82)
      Plastic; 9.0 x 5.0 inches
    - Printing plates for the Murphys' stationery, undated (Box 88, Folder 945-948)
      Metal; 2.5 x 4 and 0.5 x 2.0 inches
      Includes plate from Tiffany & Co. and "Le Bloc, Beauvais" (Paris); plates read "Gerald Murphy," "Mrs. Gerald Murphy," "Mr. and Mrs. Gerald Murphy," and "S.M."
    - Tiffany & Co. calling cards, undated (Box 88, Folder 949)
      Cardboard and paper; 3.5 x 2.5 inches
      Cards read "Mr. and Mrs. Gerald Murphy"
    - Box of "Cash's Woven Names" labels for Gerald Murphy, undated (Box 81)
      Cardboard, cotton, and twine; 3.25 x 1.5 inches
    - Miniature travel razor and razor blades, undated (Box 81)
      Metal and paper; 1.0 x 2.0 inches
    - Flag from Weatherbird, undated
      Nylon; 19.0 x 11.5 inches
    - Key to Weatherbird cabin and Mark Cross gift box, undated (Box 88, Folder 950)
      Metal and paper; 3.5 inches
    - Blue leather photograph album with gold tooling "John Charles Baoth Donnelly, June 20th, 1951"
      Leather, paper, and plastic; 10.0 x 7.5 inches
      Made by Mark Cross; album empty
    - Blue leather scrapbook with gold tooling "J.C.B.D.", circa 1951
      Leather and paper; 10.0 x 12.0 inches
      Made by Mark Cross; scrapbook empty
    - Beige leather photograph album with gold tooling, undated
    - Beige leather scrapbook with gold tooling, undated
    - Brown leather trifold photograph case, undated (Box 89, Folder 951)
      Leather and plastic; 4.5 x 3.25 inches
      Case empty
    - Brown leather trifold photograph case with gold tooling, undated (Box 89, Folder 952)
      Leather, plastic, and fabric; 4.5 x 5.0 inches
      Made by Mark Cross; case empty
    - Dog collars, undated (Box 79)
      Leather, metal and plastic; 7.0 x 1.25 and 7.0 x 0.75
      One collar in white tie design with black backing and one collar with red cubic zirconia design
    - Pencil sharpener in red leather case, undated (Box 81)
      Metal and leather
    - Pocket letter opener, undated (Box 81)
      Metal; 2.5 x 1.0 inches
      Engraved "K of C" (Knights of Columbus)
    - Miniature gold diploma engraved with "H.A.M. 1937" in box marked "Honoria" (Box 81)
      Paper and metal; 0.5 inches
      Made by Barnett & Svec Inc.
    - Seal with monogram "H.M.", undated (Box 81)
      Metal and plastic; 2.5 inches
    - Seal with monogram "P.M.", undated (Box 81)
    - Nails with decorated heads (one of a tall ship and one of a Canada goose), undated (Box 81)
      Metal and plastic; 2.0 inches
    - Round floral box, undated (Box 89, Folder 953)
      Wood and paper; 2.25 x 2.25 inches
    - Box containing dried Dogwood flower given by John Donnelly to Honoria, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 954)
      Cardboard; 2.0 x 3.0 inches
    - Miniature pipe with claw design around bowl and marked "Frank" on side, undated (Box 80)
      Plastic; 2.5 inches
    - Box with lid painted with snow scene and "Vive Monsieur Murphy", circa 1930 (Box 90, Folder 955)
    - Matchbook with initials "SWM", undated (Box 90, Folder 956)
    - "La Corona, Gran Fabrica de Tabacos" cigar box, undated (Box 90, Folder 957)
      Cardboard; 4.0 x 7.0 inches
      Cigar box depicted in Gerald Murphy's painting "Cocktail"
    - "Ramon Allones Habana" cigar box, undated (Box 91, Folder 958)
      Wood and paper; 3.75 x 6.0
    - Ed. Laurens Prince de Monaco cigarette box, circa 1920 (Box 91, Folder 959)
      Metal; 5.25 x 3.75 inches
      Note states: "brand smoked by Sara Murphy in 1920s"
    - Empty Mark Cross gift boxes and merchandise bags, undated (Box 92, Folder 960-962)
      Cardboard; 5.0 x 5.0, 4.5 x 3.25, and 6.5 x 2.5 inches
    - Exhibition mounts, undated (Box 82)
      Metal, leather, and plastic; 13 x 3, 12 x 2.5, 9 x 1.5 inches
    - Metal tube with blue wooden insert, undated (Box 82)
      Wood and metal; 5.0 x 0.5 inches
    - Wooden rods, undated (Box 82)
      Wood; 7.0 x 0.75 inches
    - Driftwood, undated (Box 82)
      Wood; 2.5 x 4.0 inches
    - Small locks and keys, undated (Box 81)
      Includes keys for Sneden's Landing
    - Metal carabiners, undated (Box 81)
    - Metal chains, undated (Box 81)
    - Round metal object, undated (Box 81)
      Metal; 1.75 x 1.75 inches
    - Lucite stand, undated (Box 81)
      Plastic; 3.5 x 2 inches
- Audiovisual Material, 1932-1999; Series VI; 1.21 linear feet (5 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be available. Consult Access Services for further information.
  The series is organized into three subseries: Phonograph Record, Home Movies, and Recordings Created and Collected by Honoria Donnelly.
  The audiovisual series contains recordings created and collected by Sara and Gerald Murphy as well as by their daughter Honoria Murphy Donnelly. The only music included in the Papers is a phonograph record entitled "All the Way Home, Carnegie Hall Recording Co."
  Among the most substantive audiovisual material is home movies dating from the 1930s and the 1940s. The Murphys created home movies, which, according to the labels, largely show the family in playful moments, such as visiting the MacLeish family for Christmas at their home in Conway, Massachusetts, sailing the Weatherbird, and playing at Saranac Lake, New York.
  The subseries of Recordings Created and Collected by Honoria Donnelly largely consists of audio recordings of Honoria Donnelly's interviews while researching her book Sara and Gerald. Among her interviewees are the Murphy family's former employees, Ernestine Leray and Henriette Géron; her aunt, Noël Haskins Murphy; and family friend Hester Pickman. Also included are audiovisual recordings of interviews given by Donnelly and programs about family friends, such as Dos Passos, Fitzgerald, Porter, and Hemingway (to which Donnelly frequently contributed).
  - Phonograph Record
    - "All the Way Home, Carnegie Hall Recording Co." (two phonograph records), undated (Box 169 (Record album storage), Folder 1548)
  - Home Movies
    - Films
      - "X-mas Conway, Bedford Coasting, Small Shots of Boat." One 16mm reel, 150 feet, roughly 4.10 minutes, 1932 (Box 173 (Cold storage))
      - "Sailing Weatherbird." One 16mm reel, 400 feet, roughly 11.6 minutes, 1933 Summer (Box 174 (Cold storage))
      - "First Spanish Trip." One 16mm film reel, 400 feet, roughly 11.6 minutes, 1933 (Box 175 (Cold storage))
      - "Second Spanish Trip." Two 16mm reels, 400 feet, roughly 11.6 minutes each, 1934 (Box 176 (Cold storage)–177 (Cold storage))
      - "Saranac Lake." One 16mm reel, 200 feet, roughly 5.33 minutes, circa 1935 (Box 178 (Cold storage))
      - "Summer 1938." One 16mm reel, 250 feet, roughly 6.56 minutes (Box 179 (Cold storage))
      - "Swan Cove." One 16mm reel, 400 feet, roughly 11.6 minutes, circa 1938 (Box 180 (Cold storage))
      - "Bad parts." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1938 (Box 181 (Cold storage))
      - "Weatherbird – Corsica and Monte Carlo." One 16mm reel, 250 feet, roughly 6.56 minutes, 1939 Summer (Box 182 (Cold storage))
      - "East Hampton, Honoria, Noël [Haskins Murphy]." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1939 (Box 183 (Cold storage))
      - "East Hampton, Honoria, Alan [Jarvis?], Lloyd [Bowers?], puppies, Gerald, Barrys." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1940 (Box 184 (Cold storage))
      - "Best picture of puppies, Alan [Jarvis?], Fanny [Brennan Myers]." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1940 Summer (Box 185 (Cold storage))
      - "Roll with Susan." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, circa 1940 (Box 186 (Cold storage))
      - "Louise [Dowdney], Honoria, puppies." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1940 (Box 187 (Cold storage))
      - "Puppies, chrysanthemums, Virginia Lake." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1940 Fall (Box 188 (Cold storage))
      - "Puppies." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1940 (Box 189 (Cold storage))
      - "New puppies and Pomona in all forms." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1941 (Box 190 (Cold storage))
      - Unidentified. One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1941 (Box 191 (Cold storage))
      - Unidentified. One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1941 September (Box 192 (Cold storage))
      - "H.M. Donnelly and W.M. Donnelly, Rushes Pictures." One 16mm reel, 250 feet, roughly 6.56 minutes, 1983 October 13 (Box 193 (Cold storage))
      - "Mr. W. Donnelly, synchronized sound, double system." One 16mm reel, 100 feet, roughly 2.46 minutes, 1983 October 13 (Box 194 (Cold storage))
      - "Boy ice skating." One 16mm reel, 30 feet, roughly 0.50 minutes, undated (Box 196 (Cold storage))
      - "Boy sailing sloops in lake." One 16mm reel, 30 feet, roughly 0.50 minutes, undated (Box 196 (Cold storage))